(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic festive mood
花咲く 浮かれモード
A festive mood like flowers blooming
史上最大級の
The biggest in history...
恋が始まりそう
...it seems like love is about to begin
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic Ukare Mode
Lyrics, Music: つんく Arrangement: 上杉洋史
Lyrics, Music: Tsunku Arrangement: Hiroshi Uesugi
毎日見かけるあの人に
To that person I see every day
…してた
...I was doing.
普段の仲間とはしゃいでる
I'm frolicking with my usual friends
目立つ人
You're someone who stands out
自転車置き場の前
In front of the bicycle parking lot
油断していたら
When I let my guard down
急に彼が携帯番号
Suddenly he gave me his phone number
メモしてくれた
He wrote it down for me
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic high-spirits mode
花咲く 地元の駅
Flowers blooming at the local station
いつもと違う
It's different from usual
景色に変わった
The scenery has changed
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic high-spirits mode
花咲く 彼もどう？
Flowers blooming, how about him too?
悟られないように
So that no one notices
メモを受け取った
I accepted the note
おうちにつくまで メモは見ずに
Not looking at the note until I get home
一目散
I'm running straight back
それでも半信半疑だし
Even so, I'm still half-doubting
変な気分
It's a strange feeling
夜の9時になったら
When it's 9 PM
電話が欲しいと
That he wants a phone call
きっぱり書いてあった
It was clearly written
そこにぐっときたな
That really moved me
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic high-spirits mode
花咲く 夜の9時
Flowers blooming at 9 PM
気になるドラマの
It's the feeling of a drama starting
始まる気配だ
that I'm curious about
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic high-spirits mode
花には勇気がいる
Flowers need courage
部屋に鍵かけて
Locking my room door
時計とにらめっこ
Having a staring contest with the clock
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic high-spirits mode
花咲く 夜の9時
Flowers blooming at 9 PM
視聴率 最大ね
The viewership rating is at its peak
心の ビッグパレード
My heart's big parade
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic high-spirits mode
花咲く 私の部屋
Flowers blooming in my room
いつもと違う
It's different from usual
景色に変わった
The scenery has changed
ロマンティック 浮かれモード
Romantic high-spirits mode
花咲く 彼もどう？
Flowers blooming, how about him too?
悟られないように
So that no one notices
恋が始まりそう
It seems like love is about to start
Yay! Kikkerikii!
Did you enjoy that?
Hello everybody, welcome! I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English -Myth-
and I welcome you to my very special Hello! Project cover song
Kiara & Friends: Spring Concert!
Woohoo! Yay!
Yes! And it is Hello! Project themed. Do you know what Hello! Project is?
Ah, I used to go to so many Hello! Project concerts back in the day.
I love Hello! Project, it's an idol agency that has several different groups like Morning Musume, Berryz Kobo, °C-ute,
and so many more! So today, I will introduce all of them to you.
Yay! And don't forget to use the hashtag #HPmeetsHoloEN so that I can look at your screenshots
and everybody gets to know even if they missed the livestream, you can maybe tell them to watch the VOD. Yay, yay, yay!
And so I kicked things off with the legendary
“Romantic Ukare Mode” (Romantic High-Spirits Mode)
by Fujimoto Miki-san, who is... oh, she wrote history! You don't even understand.
She's a Hello! Project idol legend!
So I hope that came across a little bit. Of course I'm not on her level, but you know, you know.
Okay, so besides performing many, many, many Hello! Project songs,
we'll also be having as many Hololive English members...
...as possible.
And that might even mean that we get a member...
...who you haven't seen...
...in a long, long time!
You already know, don't you?
Yes, and also we have flower crowns...
...as you can maybe tell.
Pretty, pretty, wow.
We have these yellow ones...
...but who knows, maybe we'll have...
...some other colors too...
...because Hello Project also means...
...many different colors, image colors...
...and personalities...
...and we're gonna show them with these flowers.
And one more thing, the stage.
Let's give an applause for the stage!
Woohoo, the stage!
Thank you for coming, you cutie-pooties!
Are you excited for a big concert...
...out here in this outdoor square?
Yay yay yay yay!
All right, then let's jump right into it.
Everybody, let's have a great time!
Enjoy! Woo!
うわぁー！うわぁー！
Whoa! Whoa!
Ame, you live!
And you're here as a guest!
ガチンコでいこう!
Gachinko de ikou!
Lyrics: 岩里祐穂 Music: ムラマツテツヤ
Lyrics: Yuho Iwasato Music: Tetsuya Muramatsu
Thank you!
Ame!
Happy birthday, Chawa-wa!
Thank you!
All right, let's dance!
Yay!
暴れん坊なうちらする夢に
In our wild and reckless dreams,
限界はないよ
There is no limit!
そう！ そう！
Go! Go!
そうさ 可能性100％で生まれたら
That's right, since we were born with 100% potential,
100％で生きていくぜ
We're gonna live at 100%!
泣いたり笑ったりして
We cry, we laugh,
いろんな人に出会う
And we meet all kinds of people.
大事なもの見つけたり
We find precious things,
なくしたり
And sometimes we lose them.
ハイ、ドマイ！
Hi, don't mind!
ガンガン走っていけたら
If we can keep running full speed,
そのほうが楽しんじゃん
It'll be way more fun!
そうじゃ そうじゃ！
That's right, that's right!
あれもしたい
I want to do this,
これもしたい
And I want to do that too.
行くぞ！
Here we go!
レッツ・ゴー！
Let's go!
ガチンコでいこう
Let's do this seriously!
世界に
In this world,
一人
...just for...
だけの
...the one and only...
自分
...yourself...
のために
...in the world.
大好きなことはきっと
You'll surely find the things...
きっと見つけてやれ
...the things you love!
恥ずかしがりなうちらする恋は
The love that we, the shy ones, have
ドキドキしている
Makes our hearts throb!
ドキドキ！
Thump-thump!
誰も最初は怖がりで
Everyone is a coward at first,
勇気出さなきゃ変われない
But you can't change if you don't find courage!
本当の気持ちなぜか
For some reason, my true feelings...
やせ我慢をしている
...I'm just putting on a brave face.
時間を置いてみたり
Trying to give it time,
言われたり
Or having people tell me things.
へそかい！
Is that so!
ガンガン走っていけたら
If we can keep running full speed,
そのほうが生きてんじゃん
We'll feel more alive!
ドマイ ドマイ！
Don't mind, don't mind!
あれも欲しい
I want this,
これも欲しい
And I want that too.
行くぞ！
Here we go!
レッツ・ゴー！
Let's go!
ガチンコでいこう
Let's do this seriously!
そうだよ
That's right,
やるなら今からいい
If you're gonna do it, now is the time!
我慢はできない
I can't hold back anymore,
だから もっともっとしたい
So I want to do even more!
ガンガン走っていけたら
If we can keep running full speed,
世界に一人だけの自分のために
For the one and only you in the world.
そうだよ そうだよ そうだよ
That's it, that's it, that's it!
ガチンコでいこう
Let's do this seriously!
大好きなことを きっときっと見つけてやれ
You'll surely find the things you love!
夢は負けない
My dreams won't lose!
我慢できない
I can't hold back!
だから もっともっとしたい
So I want to do even more!
泣いたり笑ったりして
We cry, we laugh,
いろんな人に
And we meet all kinds of...
La la la...
...で会う
...to meet
大事なもの見つけたり
Finding important things
失くしたり
Or losing them
はい どんまい！
Hey, don't mind!
ガンガン走って行けたら
If we can keep running forward
その方が楽しいじゃん
That would be more fun
そうじゃん そうじゃん
That's right, that's right
あれもしたい これもしたい
I want to do this, and that too
行くぞ！進め！オー！
Let's go! Move forward! Oh!
ガチンコでいこう
Let's go all out
世界に一人の
For the only one in the world
自分のために
That is yourself
大好きなことを
Find what you love
きっときっと見つけてやれ
And make sure to hold onto it
私の未来のだんな様
My Future Husband
喧嘩したい 愛したい
I want to fight, I want to love
会いたい 会いたい
I want to see you, I want to see you
クリスマスは盛り上げたい
I want to have a blast at Christmas
会いたい 会いたい
I want to see you, I want to see you
Oh no 今のままでは
Oh no, if things stay as they are
何も ヘイ 変わんない
Nothing, hey, will change
大人任せじゃダメ
Leaving it to the adults is no good
友達集めて ねえ
Gather your friends, hey
臨時会費
Special membership fee
盆暮れ正月 バレンタイン
Summer festivals, year-end, New Year's, Valentine's
一人で過ごしたくない
I don't want to spend them alone
私の未来のだんな様
My future husband
どこかに目印をつけて
Put a marker on yourself somewhere
歩いてちょうだい
And walk this way, please
寂しいわ 悔しいわ
I'm lonely, I'm frustrated
会いたい 会いたい
I want to see you, I want to see you
恋するより気楽だし
It's more carefree than being in love
だし だし
More, more
Oh no そんなことでは
Oh no, if that's the case
今より ヘイ 最悪
Things will be, hey, even worse than now
明日からでは遅い
Starting tomorrow will be too late
たったの今から ねえ
Starting right now, hey
さあ 始めよう
Come on, let's begin
身長 体重 血液型
Height, weight, blood type
こだわりとかあったけど
I used to be picky about those
素敵な未来のだんな様
My wonderful future husband
結局好きになれば好き
In the end, if I like you, I like you
まずはどこか
First, let's go somewhere
明日からでは遅い
Starting tomorrow will be too late
たったの今から ねえ
Starting right now, hey
さあ 始めよう
Come on, let's begin
身長 体重 血液型
Height, weight, blood type
こだわりとかあったけど
I used to be picky about those
素敵な未来のだんな様
My wonderful future husband
結局好きになれば好き
In the end, if I like you, I like you
盆暮れ正月 バレンタイン
Summer festivals, year-end, New Year's, Valentine's
一人で過ごしたくない
I don't want to spend them alone
私の未来のだんな様
My future husband
どこかに目印をつけて
Put a marker on yourself somewhere
歩いてちょうだい
And walk this way, please
あまのじゃく
Amanojaku
君のことなど 興味ない
I'm not interested in you at all
他の誰と 話したって
No matter who else you talk to
サッパリね 髪の毛を
Not at all... I didn't even notice...
切ったのも 知らない
...that you cut your hair
大嫌い 幸せね
I hate you. Are you happy?
自転車が 変わったね
You got a new bike
斎藤先輩と
With Saito-senpai...
すごく仲が 良いのも
...and how you're such good friends
全部 全部 興味ない
I'm not interested in any of it
話せない日だって ブルーじゃない
I'm not blue on the days we don't talk
君のことなど 興味ない
I'm not interested in you at all
遊園地に 誘われても
Even if you invite me to the amusement park
生徒会で 忙しいから
I'm busy with the student council
一度くらい 行けど
Maybe I'll go once, but
優しく されたり
Being treated kindly
髪型 褒められたり
Or having my hairstyle praised
勉強 教わったり
Being taught studies
守って くれても
Or even being protected
全部 全部 興味ない
I'm not interested in any of it
君の顔も 覚えない
I don't even remember your face
遠く 離れたり
Moving far away
喧嘩とか しちゃったり
Or getting into fights
優しく されたり
Being treated kindly
髪型 褒められたり
Or having my hairstyle praised
勉強 教わったり
Being taught studies
守って くれても
Or even being protected
全部 全部 興味ない
I'm not interested in any of it
もうすぐ 引っ越しするでしょ
You're moving soon, aren't you?
これ以上 優しくしないで
Don't be any kinder than this
嘘泣きして あげるから
Because I'll give you a fake cry
Ehh! Teggan!
Who would've thought? This is just how it goes here.
Bye bye girls!
Well that was our next big part,
the first half or so of the nice super awesome special guest segment!
The first song was... Gachinko de Ikou!
It was performed with... people and...
I want to hear you in the chat!
Ame! Ame!
That's right, yeah, I managed to finally get Ame back for a performance.
And if anyone would make that happen, you know it would be
number one teammate Takanashi Kiara, right? Of course it was.
Ah, I miss her already.
The song was from Buono!, which is a special unit that came together with
two members of Berryz Kobo and one from ℃-ute. Yes,
they're so awesome, they're so legendary.
Speaking of Berryz Kobo, after that came Watashi no Mirai no Dannasama
with special guests Ina, Ina, Ina
and Nerissa, the super tall one!
That song is one of my favorite songs from Berryz Kobo,
and it's about finding the ideal 'husbando'. 'Husband', Dannasama is husband.
The height difference from Ina and Nerissa was kind of crazy in that one.
Is that what they call a moe gap?
I think so.
And then we had Amanojaku performed by our guest Ina again
and Fuwawa and Mococo. Together they are FuwaMoco!
Bau bau bau bau! Yeah!
It's from another one of my favorite idol groups from Hello! Project called S/mileage.
They were made up of four members, but they quickly had some graduations
and added many members, and they have since been renamed to ANGERME.
Amanojaku was actually their debut song, so it's super sweet and innocent.
Fitting these members that we had, right?
I agree too.
Next up is another song, but let's head over to a new place.
The one up there. We shall go in there, okay?
Will you follow me?
Okay, I'll take the way around, I won't go directly,
I'll go there. Okay.
Follow me! Bye bye!
なんちゃって恋愛
Lyrics, Music: Tsunku Arrangement: Okubo Kaoru
Nanchatte Ren'ai (Just Kidding Romance)
Lyrics, Music: Tsunku Arrangement: Kaoru Okubo
あくびが一つ出ちゃうほど
So much so that a yawn escapes me
つまらない午後になったな
It's become a boring afternoon
ナンパとかしなきゃいられぬかな
Do I have to go out and flirt or something?
シラケちゃう
It's a real buzzkill
しばらくは元気なキャラで
For a while, I've lived with a cheerful persona
なんとなく生きてきたけど
And somehow managed to get by
気が付けば色気も出てきてるみたい
Before I knew it, I seem to have developed some sexiness
みたい
Or so it seems
ああだのこうだの私
With "this and that", I...
言うことが足りないたび
Every time words fail me
泣きたい気持ちになる ハハッ
I feel like crying, haha
Oh baby 夢も全部真剣だから
Oh baby, because even my dreams are serious
大人になる条件を 教えてほしい
I want you to tell me the requirements for becoming an adult
だけどなんだかめんどくさい
But somehow it's a bit of a hassle
そのうちテレビを買い替えないと いけないね
Before long, I'll have to buy a new TV, won't I?
なんちゃって恋愛をしたとこで
Even if I have a "just kidding" romance
寂しくなるだけ
It'll just make me lonely
それなのにぬくもりを 感じたくなる
And yet, I still want to feel some warmth
なんちゃっていい奴を演じても
Even if I act like a "just kidding" nice person
虚しくなるだけ
It'll just leave me empty
それなのに適当に 愛想笑い
And yet, I still give a half-hearted fake smile
ハンバーガー かじりながら
While biting into a hamburger
街行く人を眺めてた
I was watching the people passing by.
本当に笑い合ってる子なんて
I wonder if there are any girls
いるのかしら...
who are truly laughing together...
ヘッドホンから流れてる
Flowing from my headphones,
お気に入りの曲が繰り返し
my favorite song repeats over and over.
この歌詞は私のこと歌ってる...
These lyrics are singing about me...
望んだのと私 素直にはまれない
I can't honestly get into what I hoped for.
誰にでも合わせたい hah-ha
I want to fit in with everyone, hah-ha.
Oh Baby 明日何にするの私 何を求めてるの ah-yeah
Oh Baby, what am I doing tomorrow? What am I looking for? ah-yeah.
愛が足りない
Love is not enough.
だけど意味なく群れたりしない だってそんなの勿体ない You know
But I don't hang out aimlessly, because that's just a waste of time, you know.
愛したい
I want to love.
なんちゃって恋愛を繰り返す 女の子の気持ち
The feelings of a girl repeating make-believe romances.
誰にでも分かっちゃうわ 女の子なら
Any girl would understand.
なんちゃって色々と言うけれど 輝きたいだけ
I say all these things, but I just want to shine.
私でもなれるかしら 本物に...
I wonder if I can become the real thing...
なんちゃって恋愛をしたとこで 寂しくなるだけ
Even if I have a make-believe romance, it just makes me lonely.
それなのに温もりを 感じたくなる
And yet, I still want to feel warmth.
なんちゃっていい奴を演じても 虚しくなるだけ
Even if I pretend to be a 'nice person', it just feels empty.
それなのに適当に 愛されたい
And yet, I want to be loved in a casual way.
なんちゃって恋愛を繰り返す 女の子の気持ち
The feelings of a girl repeating make-believe romances.
誰にでも分かっちゃうわ 女の子なら
Any girl would understand.
なんちゃって色々と言うけれど 輝きたいだけ
I say all these things, but I just want to shine.
私でもなれるかしら 本物に
I wonder if I can become the real thing.
Independent Girl ～独立女子であるために～
Independent Girl ~To Be an Independent Woman~
目を覚ましてよ そんな涙を
Wake up! The one who made you shed
流させたのは 彼なんて
those tears is just some guy.
あなたのことを 愛していたら
If he really loved you,
きっとひどい事 できないはずでしょ
surely he wouldn't be able to do such a terrible thing.
おかしいよ 気付かないうち
It's strange. Before you know it,
人に振り回されちゃって
you're being jerked around by others.
服のセンスとか 髪の色まで
From your sense of fashion to the color of your hair,
誰かの言いなりになってる
you're doing whatever someone else tells you.
恋は盲目っていうよ
They say love is blind.
バッドメディシンみたいなもんよ
It's like a bad medicine.
本当の愛はそんな
Real love isn't
辛くなんかないやいやい
painful like that at all.
Independent Girl じゃなきゃダメさ
You've got to be an Independent Girl.
Ah-ah 声を聞かせてよ
Ah-ah, let me hear your voice.
誰かのものなんかじゃないんだ
We're not someone else's property.
私たち Independent
We're Independent.
Girl じゃなきゃダメさ
You've got to be a Girl.
Ah-ah こっちを向いてよ
Ah-ah, look over here.
自分の生き方くらい
Try deciding your own way of life
自分で決めてみなよ
by yourself.
ニコニコ笑う 馬鹿な女に
For you, who has stooped down to being
成り下がってる あなたなんて
a foolish woman who just smiles and nods...
本当のあなた なんかじゃないわ
...that's not the real you.
早く現実に 気付いて
Realize the truth soon.
携帯 やたらにチェックされて
Your phone is checked all the time,
身動き取れない毎日
every day you can't even move freely.
まるで奴隷みたいよ 悲しい...
You're like a slave. It's sad...
Independent Girl ~独立女子であるために~
Independent Girl ~To be an Independent Girl~
Independent girl にならなくちゃ
I have to become an independent girl
あーは　すぐに取り戻せ自分
A-ha, take yourself back immediately
自分で決めた答えはきっと正しい
The answer I decided on for myself is surely right
Independent girl にならなくちゃ
I have to become an independent girl
あーは　あなたはあなたよ
A-ha, you are you
私達の未来は自分で切り開くの
We will carve out our own future
Independent girl じゃなきゃダメさ
It has to be an independent girl
あーは　声を聞かせてよ誰か
A-ha, let me hear your voice, someone
誰かのモノなんかじゃないんだ私達
We aren't anyone's property
Independent girl じゃなきゃダメさ
It has to be an independent girl
あーは　こっちを向いてよ
A-ha, look this way
自分の生き方くらい自分で決めてみなよ
Decide your own way of life by yourself
Yay!
I got the memo. Yatta!
I got the memo. I did it!
Hello! O-yay!
私達 Independent Girls です！
We are the Independent Girls!
Yeah, we're the independent joshi! Yeah, that's right!
Yeah, we're the independent girls! Yeah, that's right!
Okay, let me please let me hear some introductions. How about we start with my senpai...
...my once senpai? How... how much of a senpai are you?
I'm your senpai by one stream.
It's like we're twins, you know? Who's born first?
True, that's a good point. Okay, I guess that would be me.
Minasan, it's me, Mori Calliope, Hololive English's rapping reaper singer-songwriter. Hello everybody!
Everyone, it's me, Mori Calliope, Hololive English's rapping reaper singer-songwriter. Hello everybody!
If you don't know me, now you do. Who's next?
Ah, the kouhai IRyS-pon here? Okay then.
Ah, the junior IRyS-pon here? Okay then.
IRyS! It's IRyS from Hololive English: Project HOPE's stays-at-home Nephilim...
...here to bring hope to this world and to Kiara.
Oh, the hope of all of us! Kouhai IRyS! Welcome!
Oh, the hope of all of us! Junior IRyS! Welcome!
Well girls, we have just performed 'Independent Girl ~独立女子であるために~'...
Well girls, we have just performed 'Independent Girl ~To be an Independent Girl~'...
...by Buono! My Buono! It's a long title.
Dokuritsu Joshi! Dokuritsu Joshi.
Independent girls! Independent girls.
And we're now inside, by the way. We're in the building that was behind previously.
It's so dark! It's like a planetarium. Pretty! Okay.
You can move in here with me if you want to! Wanna? Wanna?
Sure. I kind of want to go for a walk outside. A walk outside?
Maybe not, because don't we want to be independent girls? Why would we live together?
That's true.
Speaking of that, come back, independent ladies! Trying to be an independent girl, I don't know.
I want to ask you girls something. What makes you such an independent girl?
Oh, such a great cue. I didn't have time to prepare for this at all.
For Mori, I always was playing alone by myself at the playground. Beyond that, I had to...
Yeah, yeah, I had no friends. Oh, no friends?
Now too. You go to the playground? Oh, I mean, I kind of feel like...
...have you seen the park outside? It's so lovely. That's true.
No, for me, the main reason I think I'm an independent girl is because I do a lot of music stuff on my own.
So I write my own songs and stuff like that. Yeah, and do a lot of things myself.
So I feel like that's something an independent person has to do.
I count that. Yes. Build bit of a lone wolf.
Yeah, what about you? How are you independent? I would say...
...well, it's many things. Like for example, since last year, I own a home!
おめでとう！ But that might make some people cry right now, it's too depressing.
Congratulations! But that might make some people cry right now, it's too depressing.
Uh, but yeah, also having my own babies, aka my cats. She's a mom!
But anyway, I want to hear why IRyS is independent. Or is she not very independent at all?
Independent? あらあら！
Independent? Oh my goodness!
Independent? What makes you not independent, IRyS? Maybe we can fix it.
I... I can't open water... I can open water bottles by myself if I try really hard.
I can wake up with... with multiple alarms. I... I can... I can...
...stuff. Does it- has it turned out we sang this song to IRyS?
You have to be independent IRyS.
Teaching her a lesson.
I am so independent. I did not have my
manager feed me medicine right before this.
I saw that! I saw that!
I saw that. I heard it.
And you were like, "Can you put it right into-"
We believe you.
That sounds weird. Oh my god.
Anyway, we will continue teaching her some
lessons about independence, right? Okay.
She can't be independent for now though, so we're
going to go for a walk in the forest together.
Take me! Take me independent girl!
Okay, I'll take you.
Thanks for the invite, Kiara! It's been fun!
Bye bye! I'll teach you the ways.
Alright, come on IRyS, we're going to
go for a walk now.
Oh my god. Bye bye!
Yeah. Well, that was independent girls right there.
But going on, moving on,
I think I'll put my microphone away so I can
have a little bit more freedom with my arms
and maybe I'll attach some LEDs to this outfit.
Got to switch some batteries.
So, I'll see you in a minute!
Love take it all
Lyrics, Music: つんく♂
Lyrics, Music: Tsunku♂
思い出したくない 恋もしてきたわ
I've been in loves I don't want to remember
若気の至りってやつね
The rashness of youth, you know?
それでも後悔は しないのが私流
Even so, not having regrets is my style
自分が生きてきた道だから
Because it's the path I've walked
嘘をついてまでして 体裁取り繕って
Going so far as to lie to keep up appearances
逆に疲れないんだろうか
Don't you just get tired instead?
夢が 夢が 夢が 弾む
Dreams, dreams, dreams are bouncing
このまま引き下がらない
I won't back down like this
次の扉開けば 未来が見える
If I open the next door, I can see the future
ほら シンプルなキスくらいじゃ ごまかされないよ
Look, I won't be fooled by just a simple kiss
次のチャンス掴めば さらなるチャンス
If I grab the next chance, even more chances
ほら 複雑な青春の 糸を解すように
Look, like untangling the threads of complex youth
Love take it all
好きでもないのに ただ何となく
Even though I didn't love them, just somehow
付き合ったりもしたけれど
I've dated people like that too
起き上がれないほど 高熱出した日も
Even on days I had a fever so high I couldn't get up
会いに行きたい恋もしたよ
I've been in love where I wanted to go see them
時が 時が 時が 刻む
Time, time, time ticks on
昨日にはもう戻れない
I can't go back to yesterday anymore
次の扉開けば 未来が見える
If I open the next door, I can see the future
ほら 映画にでてきそうな セリフじゃ足りない
Look, lines that look like they're from a movie aren't enough
次のチャンス掴めば さらなるチャンス
If I grab the next chance, even more chances
ほら 誰もまだ通ってない 新たなる扉
Look, a new door that no one has passed through yet
Love take it all
次の扉開けば 未来が見える
If I open the next door, I can see the future
ほら シンプルなキスくらいじゃ ごまかされないよ
Look, I won't be fooled by just a simple kiss
次のチャンス掴めば さらなるチャンス
If I grab the next chance, even more chances
ほら
Look
忘れない　青春の　一途な想いを
I won't forget the earnest feelings of youth.
Love take it all!
Thank you!
青春コレクション
Youth Collection
最新の洋服に着替えた
I changed into the latest clothes.
こんな日はなんだか　街に出て歩きたい
On a day like this, I want to walk around town.
風吹いて　前髪　乱れても
Even if the wind blows and my bangs get messy,
それでもいいよね　私　変わりたいの
That's fine, right? I want to change.
寂しい夜につながる　秘密の場所がある
There's a secret place connected to lonely nights.
Uh yeah!
そう　私達の絆
Yes, our bond.
輝け　夢があるから
Shine, because there are dreams.
胸張って生きて行けるんでしょう
We can live with our heads held high, right?
大人にならなきゃね
We have to grow up.
我が儘しちゃって反省
I regret being selfish.
輝け　今日の私を
Shine, the me of today.
胸張って未来の私も
So the future me can live
後悔しないように
with my head held high and no regrets.
信じて　歩こう My Stage
Believe and walk, My Stage.
Oh yeah!
青春コレクション
Youth Collection!
最近ね　閃き　冴えてる
Lately, my inspiration has been sharp.
新しい友情に　出会えたりもしたし
I've also found new friendships.
いつも行く　あの店の　あいつは
That guy at the shop I always go to,
確かに格好いいよね　話しかけちゃおうかな
He's certainly cool, maybe I'll talk to him.
どっちも譲り合わずに　喧嘩になったわ
Neither back down, so we ended up in a fight.
Uh yeah!
どうやって謝ろうかな
How should I apologize?
輝け　愛があるから
Shine, because there is love.
そうやって許し合えるんでしょう
That's how we can forgive each other, right?
ネガティブ言っていても
There's no point in
いい事なんてないし
saying negative things.
輝け　今日の地球も
Shine, today's Earth too.
胸張って手を取り合おうよ
Let's hold hands with our heads held high.
家族の言葉を信じて　歩こう My Stage
Believe in your family's words and walk, My Stage.
Oh yeah!
青春コレクション
Youth Collection!
輝け　愛があるから
Shine, because there is love.
そうやって許し合えるんでしょう
That's how we can forgive each other, right?
ネガティブ言っていても
There's no point in
いい事なんてないし
saying negative things.
輝け　今日の地球も
Shine, today's Earth too.
胸張って手を取り合おうよ
Let's hold hands with our heads held high.
家族の言葉を信じて　歩こう My Stage
Believe in your family's words and walk, My Stage.
Oh yeah!
青春コレクション
Youth Collection!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Gigi Murin!
Cecilia Immergreen!
Raora Panthera! Woo!
And we are... JUSTICE!
JUSTICE!
Just like that!
GET THAT!
JUSTICE!
Okay, JUSTICE! You girls will have to work a little bit more on your sync...
...but besides that, beautiful!
Yeah! Yeah, man!
So, we just had a beautiful song, a little bit of a performance together.
It was like your first time in, like, 3D cardboard.
Yeah! I'm so happy to be 2D!
I think our dancing was a bit flat.
It was beautiful! Sometimes you gotta get on the floor, you already have that down.
So, we sang "Seishun Collection" from Morning Musume.
And as you noticed in the beginning of the song, we had some messages lying there...
...that were written by these cutie-patooties.
So let's have a little bit of a look at those messages, shall we?
I'm gonna get mine.
Yay! Let's look! Let's look!
Okay, so I'll start with introducing my message.
Love, unconditionally. Thanks for coming! by Wawa
Mine's a bit more generic or something, I don't know, this is not really towards anybody.
But it says: "Love, unconditionally. Thanks for coming!"
...By Wawa." Yay!
Yay! Kawaii!
And now, please, in your usual order, tell me about your message and what you wrote on it.
Oh, I wrote "Love You!" to Kiwawa, and then these little flowers around it...
Love You! -Liz
...to represent us as JUSTICE.
Because, yeah, we love everyone. Yay! Wow!
Aww, so cute!
I'm so happy we could be part of your song. Thank you.
Thank you!
All right, what else have we got? Who's next?
Mine says "OTSUKARE KIWAWA!!" because you worked so hard.
LOVE OTSUKARE KIWAWA!! I love you too
And I'm happy to be here. And L-O-V-E! I love you too!
Cute! And who else? What else do we have?
I wrote mine in German! I wrote "Vielen Dank! Kiara-Senpai!"
Vielen Dank! Kiara-Senpai! Hab dich lieb! Cecilia
Thank you very much! Kiara-Senpai! Love you! Cecilia
"Hab dich lieb!"
"Love you!"
Yay! And last but not least?
I wrote mine in Italian for you! "Ti amo Kiara!"
I wrote mine in Italian for you! "I love you, Kiara!"
TI AMO KIARA!! Thank you for being an amazing SENPAI!! By RAORA PANTHERA
I LOVE YOU KIARA!! Thank you for being an amazing SENPAI!! By RAORA PANTHERA
Thank you for being an amazing Senpai!
Thank you! I'm so happy that we have, you know, I took your first time. Yay!
Yay!
Thank you for taking my first time.
Yeah, all on stream. It was so much fun.
And with that, unfortunately, I have to already send you out because we got some stuff to do.
What?
Thank you JUSTICE so much for coming!
No problem! Thank you Kiara! Next time in 3D! Bye bye!
Bye bye! Bye!
Oh! It's turning night. How romantic!
Well, we are in the home stretch now, so stay with me until the very end!
Go-Go Fight!
一つ 二つ 大きく回せ
One, two, rotate it big
三つ 四つ さあ行こう！
Three, four, let's go!
Go-Go Fight!
La la la la la la 愛の歌声が
La la la la la la, the singing voices of love
聞こえてくるから
Are coming to be heard
恋するだけなら なんとかなるけど
If it's just falling in love, I can manage somehow, but...
愛するとなるとね
...when it comes to loving...
勇気も必要 それより相手よね
...courage is also necessary. More than that, a partner!
いない ない？
None? None?
気づけば夏だし そのうち冬だし
Before I know it, it's summer, and soon it'll be winter
なんだか切ないな
It's somehow painful
結局姉貴と毎日バイキング
In the end, it's every day at the buffet with my big sister
Go-Go Fight!
友達みんな彼といちゃいちゃ
All my friends are flirting with their boyfriends
くっついたり別れたり
Sticking together and breaking up
軽くね？
A bit light, right?
本当の恋愛はそんな簡単じゃん...
True love isn't that easy...
見つからないはずよ
You won't find it.
はばたこう
Let's flap our wings.
未来は自分の手の中さ
The future is in our own hands.
胸を張って Yea!
Stand tall, yeah!
ライバルは...
My rival is...
...弱気で後ろ向きな私
...the timid and pessimistic me.
簡単にゃ負けない
I won't lose easily.
夢見てるだけじゃ夢は叶わない 分かっちゃいるけどね
Just dreaming won't make dreams come true, I know that.
通学通勤毎日着る服を 選ぶだって頭使うわ
Even choosing what to wear every day takes some thinking.
身長伸びるのすっかり止まって 体重増えるのに
My height has stopped growing, but my weight goes up.
お菓子をやめてもアイス食べちゃう
Even if I quit snacks, I still end up eating ice cream.
超トキハは早い
The Super Tokiwa is fast.
ミニをはいたら
When I wear a mini skirt...
先生焼いてた
...I made the teacher jealous.
本当の理由は分かんねえだろうな
You probably don't know the real reason.
そういうブーブー友情なくしてゆけば
If we lose that kind of boo-boo friendship...
いいとこなくなるよ
...the good parts will be gone.
はばたこう
Let's flap our wings.
誰にも負けない楽しさで
With a joy that's second to none.
取り戻すんだ
We'll take it back.
悔しけりゃ
If you're frustrated...
鼻水混じりの涙とか
...tears mixed with a runny nose...
流しちゃえばいいじゃん
...it's okay to let them flow.
Go go! Pai!
はばたこう
Let's flap our wings.
未来は自分の手の中さ
The future is in our own hands.
胸を張って Yea!
Stand tall, yeah!
ライバルは...
My rival is...
...弱気で後ろ向きな私
...the timid and pessimistic me.
簡単にゃ負けない
I won't lose easily.
ひとつふたつ大きく回って
One, two, turn around in a big way.
みっつよっつ最高
Three, four, this is the best!
ラララララ愛の歌声が
La la la la la, the singing voices of love...
聞こえてくるから
...are starting to reach my ears.
Go go! Pai!
Oh~
PERFUME
Music: Asteroid Music Team (Johnny R, monii, Ari) Lyrics: monii
Arrangement: Johnny R, Ari, monii
It's simple
You gotta do it like
Mmm~
Okay Hey~
I been out of luck
I been stayin' up
Praying for anyone to hear
Hear the beating drums
Of my heart give up
I don't know what to do
Feel the rhythm, call me on my bluff
Can't die no not this way [no~]
Hopeless girl, haven't I had enough?
N-no-no-no
Cause I'm a shinin' diamond
From nothin to brilliant, oh my
Oh I do it casually
Levelin' me up
With a shade of violet
Tell you my secret
How I [I-I-I]
Put that lipstick on me [stick on me]
Oh a new improved girl, my-
Perfume, that's what I need, what I need
Got that perfume on~
Got that perfume-fume-fume on me
Got that per-per-perfume on you
Got that perfume on me, on me
I never could define what I could be so I
Went on a broken dreamer
Uh, puttin' every piece of me back, I'm free
Spent so much time just waiting, crying [Crying]
Why [Why]
But would you be born if you weren't meant for somethin' greater, baby?
Good [Good], bye [Bye]
Bye sixteen, these years have flown by really
Shinin' diamond
From nothin to brilliant, oh my
Oh I do it casually
Levelin' me up
With a shade of violet
Tell you my secret
How I [I-I-I]
Put that lipstick on me [stick on me]
Oh a new improved girl, my -
Perfume, that's what I need, what I need
Got that perfume on ~
I-I-I still feel those
Sinking thoughts, reckless emotions
I-I-I know there's
No closed door I can't open
[Girl, girl, girls so perfect]
[Don't don't don't don't doubt it]
On me
Put that lipstick on me [stick on me]
Oh a new improved girl, my -
Perfume, that's what I need, what I need
Got that perfume on ~
Got that perfu-fume-fume on me
Got that per-per fume-fume on you
Got that perfume on me, on me
Wee!
Yippee! That was my new song!
But before that, before we go into that, I shall explain.
Before the new song, we had...
...one of my favorite songs from my favorite idol group Berryz Kobo...
...'RIVAL', which you know...
...that had a really awesome formation, right? It was so fun with like...
...turning around in like different timings and everything.
Really difficult, but really fun, and I think it will look beautiful to you guys. I hope so!
Well, besides that...
another song with many members, or members, many people in one place...
...was my new song, PERFUME!
Yay, yay, yay, yay!
It will be released today!
And the jacket is here! Ta-da!
Wah wah wah!
Kind of like... it is... I wanted it to be like this...
...so it doesn't give away any hint of anime or so. It's just a perfume.
I wonder what smell it is.
Hmm, here.
Here, smell my armpits.
Then you will find out. Ah, stinky! Ah!
Okay, well, that's Perfume.
Yeah, and the music video will also come out after this.
The premiere, you may have already seen that it's up.
It's about to begin anytime soon, so be ready for it. It's gonna be really beautiful again...
...with different new 3D outfits, maybe perhaps one that I designed as well.
And maybe one that Ora-da designed. Yeah!
That's right, giving away all the secrets already now.
Okay, well...
...yeah, I hope you really enjoyed it. It was really tough, Perfume practice.
I practiced so much on it, and if you maybe noticed, I had even more back dancers than last time.
Last time was four...
...and I was the fifth one, was I? And now it's six...
...and I'm the seventh one.
So I wanted things to look even more complicated and more interesting.
I hope I managed to do that, and I hope you liked it.
And that was the only song today that is not Hello! Project.
And even though probably usually makes more sense for me to end it on my new original song...
...since this is all Hello! Project themed...
...we will still end it with one more song...
...with a Hello! Project song, one of my favorite ones from ℃-ute.
And it's called 'Bye Bye Bye'.
So to you I also say: Bye Bye Bye! Thank you for watching!
Enjoy the last song!
Woo!
勝手なイメージ 決めつけないで
Don't judge me with your selfish image
確信を見てよ get it on
Look at the certainty, get it on
それでも私は 噂をされても
Even so, even if there are rumors about me
そんなの気にせず on my way
I won't care and go on my way
踊りましょう 止まらないわ
Let's dance, it won't stop
踊りましょう 忘れるまで yeah yeah yeah
Let's dance until we forget, yeah yeah yeah
言葉で認めちゃって
Admit it with words
心の中じゃダメダメ
It's no good just in your heart
よくあることじゃないか
Isn't it a common thing?
everyone
こんなに努力したって
Even if I put in this much effort
すぐには出ない結果に
Results that don't come out immediately
ムカついてるの何故だろう
I wonder why I'm getting annoyed
...楽しもう
...Let's have fun
Bye Bye Bye 元気よく行こうぜ
Bye Bye Bye, let's go with energy
出来るだろう
We can do it, right?
Bye Bye Bye 自由に羽ばたけ
Bye Bye Bye, flap your wings freely
膨らまそう
Let's make it grow
Bye Bye Bye 未来に向かって
Bye Bye Bye, towards the future
Bye Bye Bye Bye Bye
なんとか気分を高めてみたわ
I've tried to raise my mood somehow
いい雰囲気ね　けれども
It's a nice atmosphere, however
回りはいつも色々言うわ
People around me always say things
そんなの気にせず ON MY WAY
Without worrying about that, I'm on my way
踊りましょう　止まらないわ
Let's dance, it won't stop
踊りましょう　忘れるまで
Let's dance until we forget
YEAH YEAH YEAH YEAH
恋した時はなんか
When I fell in love, somehow
頭の中がキラキラ
My head was sparkling
輝きながら全身 A BEAUTIFUL
Glowing and my whole body is beautiful
恋した後はだって
Because after falling in love
それはそれでスッキリ
That was refreshing in its own way
明日に向かって駆け出すよ
I'll start running towards tomorrow
TAKE CONTROL
Bye Bye Bye 優しく生きろ
Bye Bye Bye, live gently
抱きしめろ
Embrace it
Bye Bye Bye 素直に行こうぜ
Bye Bye Bye, let's go honestly
出来るだろう
We can do it, right?
Bye Bye Bye 胸トキメかせて
Bye Bye Bye, making my heart flutter
夢抱こう
Let's have a dream
Bye Bye Bye 自分信じたい
Bye Bye Bye, I want to believe in myself
Bye Bye Bye Bye Bye
GET ME UP
WHEN YOU GET ME UP
TAKE CONTROL
Bye Bye Bye 優しく生きろ
Bye Bye Bye, live gently
抱きしめろ
Embrace it
Bye Bye Bye 素直に行こうぜ
Bye Bye Bye, let's go honestly
出来るだろう
We can do it, right?
YEAH YEAH
Bye Bye Bye 胸トキメかせて
Bye Bye Bye, making my heart flutter
夢抱こう
Let's have a dream
Bye Bye Bye 自分信じたい
Bye Bye Bye, I want to believe in myself
Bye Bye Bye Bye Bye